PEACEMAKER: Previously
in The Suicide Squad...
AMANDA WALLER:
This is Christopher Smith,
known as Peacemaker.
His father was a soldier
who trained his son how to kill
from the moment he was born.
You fail to follow my orders
and I detonate
the explosive device
in the base of your skull.
Your mission
is to destroy every trace
of Project Starfish.
I cherish peace
with all my heart.
- (GROANS)
- (GRUNTS)
I don't care how many men,
women, and children
I need to kill to get it.
RATCATCHER: Who are you going
to show that to?
Press. People deserve to know.
I can't let you
do that, Colonel.
Miss Waller charged me
with making sure
those records
don't level this building.
- (PIPE CLANGS)
- (BOTH GRUNT)
(GROANS, CHOKES)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(WEAKLY) "Peacemaker."
What a joke.
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(EXPLOSION)
(GROANS)
Project Starfish.
It's headed towards the city,
and I think it wants to feed
on as many people as it can.
WALLER: Not our problem.
We've achieved the objective.
What are you doing,
Task Force X?
Turn around now, goddamn it!
This is your last
motherfuckin' warning!
- (CONTROLS BEEPING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (JOHN ECONOMOS EXHALES HEAVILY)
- Task Force X.
Your clearest path
is Calle Aguero.
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
- (HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
DOCTOR: You're shot
and a building falls on you,
and all you have to replace
is a clavicle?
You're the luckiest man alive.
(SIGHS)
- Can I ask you something, Doc?
- Sure.
Can you maybe up the contrast
on the X-ray a little more
to show the definition
in my muscles?
This makes me look like one
of those guys
who works out
only thinking about bulk.
I put a lot of time
into my small muscle groups,
and according to this,
it was just... wasted effort.
It's not for
your Tinder profile, Chris.
You've healed well,
but you're still gonna have
to take it easy.
Try to avoid lifting
your right elbow
- above your shoulder.
- Sure.
So, as long as you agree
to keep up
with the physical therapy,
I'm discharging you.
So, I can leave?
Go home.
Enjoy life.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT)
Psst.
Jamil!
I don't have any weed
on me, man.
- That was a one-time thing--
- It's not that, man.
Doctor said I was free to go.
- Congratulations?
- Jamil, you cool?
- What does that mean?
- Dude, can I trust you?
- No.
- No?
Uh, I don't know you, man!
- Dude, I really need
somebody I can trust--
- Don't trust me, man.
We smoked weed together, man.
I was in a fuckin' wheelchair!
I can't pretend like
that wasn't a nice moment,
but that doesn't make me trustworthy.
- I ain't trustworthy worth shit.
- What?
Why do you think
I'm mopping floors, bro?
- I went to MIT.
I don't like the responsibility.
- (MUTTERS)
- You went to MIT?
- Oh, yeah.
- The fuck are you doing here?
- That's my fucking point, man!
Why aren't you listening to me?
Fine! Fuck it.
Don't be trustworthy,
just let me ask you a question,
and don't tell anybody
about it, okay?
I would never betray a secret.
That is the opposite
of everything
you've been saying.
Truth is,
I'm supposed to be in prison.
- For what?
- Superhero shit.
- (CHUCKLES) You're a superhero?
- PEACEMAKER: Yeah.
You're kinda bulky to be
a superhero, aren't you?
Bulky? What the fuck
you mean, "bulky"?
Well, most superheroes
have a gymnast body.
- They're ready to go.
- I'm ready to go!
- What superhero are you?
- Peacemaker.
- Get outta here, motherfucker!
- You a fan?
There's no superhero
called Peacemaker.
- Dude, I'm fuckin' famous.
- Not that famous.
- Aquaman, he's famous.
- Fuck Aquaman!
No, man, don't say that.
Why say that?
He bangs chicks? Good for him.
He fucks dudes?
Got no problem with that.
He starts fuckin' fish?
That's taking it a step too far.
- Aquaman fucks fish?
- Yeah.
- I don't believe it.
- (SCOFFS)
A guy on Twitter
works for the aquarium,
said for 50 bucks,
he brings him in the back
so he can have his way
with a sturgeon.
I refuse to believe that.
And I refuse to believe
that @PepetheFrog89
is lying to me for no reason.
Fine. If you're a superhero,
what were you in prison for?
Integrity.
I made a vow to have peace,
no matter how many people
I have to kill to get it.
- Oh, Peacemaker!
- Yes!
- You're that racist superhero!
- No!
- You only kill minorities, man!
- (PEACEMAKER CHUCKLING)
I killed a fair amount
of white people too!
The ratio is suspect,
is all I have to say!
- If somebody's
committing a crime...
- Yes?
...am I supposed to control
what their ethnicity is?
No. But you need
to watch white people
as closely
as you watch people of color,
so you see more of them
committing crimes!
Fine. That's--
That's a good point.
I will trust white people
less in the future,
and kill a higher percentage
of 'em. Are you satisfied?
Yes. Thank you.
Now, what do you need?
Doctor said I was free to go,
so technically,
I should go back to prison.
What I need to know is,
on the DL, is there anybody
out there looking for me?
JAMIL: Not that I heard of, man.
- No cops outside, nothin'?
- I ain't seen no cops.
I'm thinkin'... I can just go?
Why not?
♪ (HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SCOFFS)
Guy's a total douchebag.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (INTENSE ROCK MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Go. Drive.
Yes! (GRUNTS)
♪ ("DO YA WANNA TASTE IT"
BY WIG WAM PLAYING) ♪
♪ Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it? ♪
♪ Get it on, get it on top
Make a move extreme ♪
♪ Make a pose
It's a shortcut to your dreams ♪
♪ I float straight to the stars
On that flying thing ♪
♪ Getting high, getting brave
Getting snow-blind ♪
♪ Game set, go
Pick a tune, chick harpoon ♪
♪ In a world beyond ♪
♪ Get a beat, got a heat
On a phony string ♪
♪ Tear your world apart
Once the magic starts ♪
♪ Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it? ♪
♪ What's going up
Must come down ♪
♪ Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it? ♪
♪ Baby, you're losing ground ♪
♪ Blind to what
You'll soon become ♪
♪ The mirror lies
The whole world's wrong ♪
♪ But you
Dancing with blinkers on ♪
♪ Throw your dog
The invisible bone ♪
♪ Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it? ♪
♪ What's going up
Must come down ♪
♪ Do ya really wanna
Do ya really wanna taste it? ♪
♪ Baby, you're losing ground ♪
♪ Blind to what
You'll soon become ♪
♪ The mirror lies
The whole world's wrong ♪
♪ But you
Dancing with blinkers on ♪
♪ Throw your dog
The invisible bone ♪
(SCREECHES)
- ♪ (SONG ENDS) ♪
- (SCREECHING CONTINUES)
- (TRAFFIC NOISE)
- (BIRDSONG)
(DOOR OPENING)
- KEEYA ADEBAYO: Oh.
- I thought I was gonna be
like James Bond now.
- We made it. Hey. Come on.
- (SIGHS)
Yes.
- (BARKS)
- Does this look like James Bond
to you?
- KEEYA: Come on.
- Man, I wanted champagne
in the bathtub,
and some Octopussies and shit.
Okay, girl, you better not be
getting any Octopussies
- while we're up here.
- (CHUCKLES)
What is an Octopussy anyway?
Uh, that's who Maud Adams
played in the movie.
KEEYA: Okay,
so she had eight pussies?
(CHUCKLES) As far as I know,
she only had one pussy.
- That's just her name.
- (CHUCKLES) Okay.
This might be a good time
for me to bring up...
I've been thinkin'.
If we have a kid,
I'd like to name her Octopussy.
- (CHUCKLES) Oh, is that so?
Really?
- Yes so. And if it's a boy,
- Sharknado.
- (CHUCKLES) Oh, okay.
Well, I hope
then that it's a boy,
because, um, I don't think
my parents would be too happy
with a granddaughter
named "Octopussy."
- Really? 'Cause I think...
- Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
...Lois and Chuck
would love that. (CHUCKLES)
- (EXHALES SHARPLY)
- What's wrong?
- ♪ (FORLORN MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- Just worried.
This job of yours,
it might be dangerous, or--
They got me filing papers
and making reservations.
I hope it stays that way.
Keeya, this is just a paycheck.
It's just for now.
I know that I'm not made
for this shit.
I'll save up a little,
then we'll go back home.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- You promise?
- I got you. (CHUCKLES)
I got you back.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(PHONE BUZZING)
I gotta go.
- Right now?
- LEOTA ADEBAYO: Yeah.
- Okay. Love you.
- LEOTA: Love you too.
- (DOOR OPENING, CLOSING)
- (SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- CAB DRIVER: Here?
- Yeah.
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
So, uh--
So I have this. It's, uh,
it's Corto Maltese money.
But I have no idea
how much it is.
Come on. You look
like a scratch lottery guy.
Make a game of it.
Take it to the bank.
See how much it's worth.
Maybe it's 50 cents,
but maybe it's a million bucks.
It ain't a million bucks.
What's in the bag?
(ENGINE REVVING)
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(DOG BARKING)
(DISTANT SHOUTING)
(LOCK CLICKS, RATTLES)
(DOG CONTINUES BARKING)
(SIGHS)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING, SHOUTING)
(DOG BARKING)
(GRUNTS)
- (HEAVY THUD)
- (GROANS) Ah, fuck. Ah, fuck.
(GROANS)
(EXHALING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)
(GROANS)
Dad?
Fuck!
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- VIGILANTE: (OVER PHONE)
Yo, man,
it's Vigilante, what up?
VIGILANTE: Uh, I was wondering
if you wanted to go out
on a team-up tonight.
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- VIGILANTE: Peacemaker!
Uh, It's your BFF
Vigilante here.
- What's goin' on, man?
- (SCOFFS)
VIGILANTE: Uh, what do
you say we go cruise
some crime and some bitches,
whichever comes first?
Uh, BFF stands
- for "Best Friends For--"
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- (AUDIENCE CHEERING OVER TV)
- VIGILANTE: P, it's V!
Are you watching
this game, dude? It is so--
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- VIGILANTE: Dude, uh,
I realize
in that last message, uh,
I called you P and me V,
as if you were a penis
and I was a vagina.
Uh, that, like, definitely
was-- It was not my intention--
- (MUTTERS)
- (PHONE BEEPING)
VIGILANTE: Peacemaker,
it's Vigilante.
I just got the scoop
on a big heroin shipment
coming in tonight!
- Let's go down there...
- Dude, don't be saying
that shit on my phone, man!
- What the fuck?
- ...motherfuckers' heads off!
- (PHONE BEEPING)
- (SIGHS)
- (GUN COCKING)
- Stay where you are, Smith.
- ♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (GUN COCKING)
(DOOR OPENING)
Fuck.
Fuck! I knew it was fucking
too good to be true!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
My life fuckin' sucks.
I mean...
Ah, fuck! Ah, nah, I'm fu--
I'm-- I'm-- I'm good.
I'm fucking-- I'm good.
Fuck!
You only served four years
of your 30-year sentence,
and you thought we were just
gonna let you go scot-free?
Yeah. I killed Rick Flag
for you people!
No one ever told you
to kill Flag.
Waller said do whatever I had
to do to make sure
those Project Starfish files
didn't get out.
- I made the only choice I could.
- (BOTTLES CLINKING)
Funny, for you,
how often the only choice
and killing people coincides.
- (CLANKING CONTINUES)
- What the fuck is he doing?
I have low blood sugar, okay?
So I'm dizzy.
You showed you were loyal.
You're a born killer
with expertise
in every weapon
known to humankind,
and you've had experience
in black ops around the globe,
so I'm giving you the chance
to stay out of prison
- and work for me.
- (SCOFFS) And you are?
Name's Murn.
- Clemson Murn?
- That's right.
I report directly
to Amanda Waller.
This is Harcourt,
who you may know
from Waller's team
at Belle Reve.
She'll be your handler
in the field.
John Economos,
who you may also know,
is tech and tactics.
Hey, dude, you're eating
four-year-old olives
- out of my fuckin' fridge.
- (GAGS)
And this is our new recruit,
Leota Adebayo,
which means she'll be doing
most everything else.
Glad to be here.
Ready to kick some ass, sir.
And really lookin' forward
to gettin' to know all of you.
Even you, Peacemaker.
Uh, even though you're not
the best guy in the world.
And Economos, you seem like
you're very easy to talk to.
- (CHUCKLES)
- LEOTA: So I look forward
to working with you.
Harcourt, I feel like,
because we're
the only women here,
we have to have
each other's back.
Anything you need, I got you.
And, Mr. Murn, I have to say
your outfits are really dapper.
I'm really excited to be here,
and I promise
you're not gonna regret this.
I know inside my mind
I'm not supposed
to be giving a speech,
but sometimes my mouth just does
what it wants, so...
Close mouth.
I'm bitin' my tongue right now.
Not gonna talk again.
(WHISPERS) I'm done talking.
(SCOFFS) What's the op?
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Domestic situation,
known as Project Butterfly.
As I recall, you guys
aren't particularly creative
with the case file names.
Project Starfish
was a giant walkin' starfish.
So, what, am I fighting
a Mothra now? (CHUCKLES)
I am?
I'm fightin' a Mothra? What the
fuck do I fight a Mothra with?
That's not what it is.
- Can I get a jetpack?
- No.
How the fuck am I supposed
to fight a Mothra
- without a jetpack?
- It's not a Mothra.
Still, my desire
for a jetpack remains,
'cause you got me
all excited about it.
We need you to do contract work.
- Kill people?
- Bad people.
- Whom we call Butterflies.
- (EXHALES) What if I say no?
You'll have to return
to Belle Reve.
What's to keep me
from splittin'?
We still have that bomb
in your head
to track you with,
and if that fails,
we'll blow you the hell up.
(SIGHS)
(INHALES SHARPLY) We'll meet you
for dinner tonight.
Seven-thirty at-- Where is it?
Fennel Fields
on Manchester Road.
And the mozzarella sticks...
(CLICKS FINGERS) ...are dope.
Enjoy my food, Dye-Beard.
- (SCOFFS) It's not dyed.
- (CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah, sure.
Hard edge of two-tone gray
and Magic Marker brown,
- that's natural.
- (CHUCKLES) No.
I'll be there.
I just gotta swing
by my dad's and get Eagly.
Who's Eagly?
Don't you do your research?
He's my sidekick.
♪ ("WELCOME TO THE CHURCH
OF ROCK AND ROLL"
BY FOXY SHAZAM PLAYING) ♪
♪ Welcome to the Church
Of rock and roll ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(DOG BARKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You that Peacemaker guy?
- Yeah.
- Evil supervillain.
Not a supervillain.
That's a misconception.
- I'm a superhero.
- (LAUGHS)
Batman is a superhero.
Yeah? Joe Blaggadashiocentro
is a dude workin'
- in his fuckin' garden.
- Joe who?
Point is just 'cause some other
dumb motherfucker is out there
with shears, clippin' roses,
doesn't mean you aren't, huh?
If you're gonna make up
a person,
why make up a person
with such a long name?
I'm so sorry,
I don't spend
all my fucking time
thinking of realistic-sounding
last names,
you wrinkly old fuck!
Hey, Dad.
(SIGHS)
(SCOFFS) Fuck you.
MAN OVER TV:
Below their lying,
liberal human faces
lurk extraterrestrial beings,
who want nothing other
than our civilization to fail!
They are among us.
I don't get enough attention,
I gotta have you
chattin' up my fruity neighbors?
Guy was talking to me!
He was being a total 'nad.
- Got out of prison.
- You don't say?
It's been kind of a rough go
for me lately, Dad. I was...
laid out in the hospital
for, like, five months.
♪ (GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Somebody shot me.
A building fell on me.
AUGGIE SMITH:
You let somebody shoot you?
(LAUGHS) It's not like I invited
him to come shoot me, Dad.
Pathetic.
(SIGHS)
- New lamp?
- AUGGIE: Huh?
- The-- The lamp, is it new?
- No. It's three months old.
- Been in prison for four years.
- Don't make it no newer.
You know, I asked you
to cancel my phone service.
It was still on.
I've been paying for service
for years 'cause you forgot.
Oh, it's my fault now
you fucked up
- and went to prison?
- That's not what I'm sayin'.
- Then what are you sayin'?
- It's my service.
- I got no money.
- Jesus Christ.
You're a fuckin' pussy.
- You been takin' Eagly out?
- Yeah.
Where is he?
- (SCREECHES)
- Eagly.
- ♪ (TENDER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(GASPS)
(EAGLY CHATTERING)
- Who's a good boy?
- (SCREECHES)
Yeah? Who's Daddy's boy?
(CHUCKLES)
Dad, look how excited he is.
(CHUCKLING)
- Dad, he's just awesome, right?
- (SCREECHING)
- ♪ (MUSIC SWELLS) ♪
- Oh, my God.
He's-- He's hugging me.
He's hugging me.
- This is fuckin' amazing.
- (EAGLY SQUAWKS)
Dad! Grab my phone,
I don't wanna move.
Dad?
- (SUBDUED SCREECH)
- Dad?
(METAL CLANGING)
You think it makes
this noise all the time?
LEOTA: Yeah, I don't know.
- (DISTANT SIRENS BLARING)
- (DOOR OPENING, CLOSING)
Hey, new girl,
get your shit off there.
LEOTA: Damn.
This is the only desk with sun.
Take the one in the middle.
(STEADY DRIPPING)
EMILIA HARCOURT: I don't know
what you did
to piss off Amanda Waller,
but she's definitely fucking me
and John with this gig.
What agency did you get
transferred from?
"Fucking you" how?
We helped Task Force X
during Project Starfish,
and this is her way
of getting back at us.
LEOTA: Yeah, I don't think so.
Hey, new girl's an expert
over here, John.
Well, she's entitled
to her opinion.
- Thank you.
- Her stupid fuckin' opinion.
Oh, sweet, we have a piano.
That's useful for black ops.
This is the worst HQ
of all time.
(METAL CLANGING)
You guys hear that, right?
It's not just me?
- We hear what?
- The fuckin' pi-- Oh.
Nice gaslighting.
(CHUCKLES)
- You'll get a kick
out of this, Dad.
- (EAGLY SQUAWKS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Guy I was working with,
Bloodsport, big,
tough motherfucker, mercenary,
all these weapons and shit.
We find out
he's got a rat phobia.
And not just--
not just any phobia.
I mean like pure terror,
screamin' like a little girl.
(CHUCKLES)
And this other member
of the team, Ratcatcher,
- she controls rats!
- (EAGLY SCREECHING)
PEACEMAKER: And, Dad, Dad,
you know how he got the phobia?
Of course I don't fuckin' know
how he got it.
He was tortured!
His own father tortured him
by lockin' him in a crate
for 24 hours with nothing
but starving rats!
- (LAUGHS)
- Right?
- PEACEMAKER: We--
(CHUCKLING) He had
these horrible acne scars.
- Scars! (LAUGHS)
- PEACEMAKER: Yeah! Yeah,
but they weren't!
They were rat bites
from when the rats
- would gnaw at his flesh
when he was a little kid!
- (EAGLY SCREECHES)
That's-- It's funny, right?
- (CACKLES, COUGHS)
- Dad?
- (COUGHS)
- I'll get-- I'll get water.
- (SCREECHES)
- (COUGHS, CHUCKLES)
- Here, here, here.
- (CHUCKLES)
- (SIGHS)
- (CHUCKLES) Hmm.
- This fag that was afraid
of the rats...
- Yeah.
Please God don't tell me
he was the one who shot you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SQUAWKS)
You know, a lot of what happened
in Corto Maltese
is confidential.
How did my fucking sperm...
grow into a nancy boy like you?
- ♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- (EXHALES DEEPLY)
Look, I just came by
to get Eagly
and see if you had
another helmet for me.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(THRUMMING)
(MACHINERY WHIRRING)
(SIGHS)
This one has
full-body force field.
This has sonic blast capabilities.
You need to breathe underwater,
then this is the one for you.
And, uh, this one
has X-ray vision.
I didn't make these things
while you were in prison.
These are all from before.
I know.
I never gave you
a second thought
- while you were in there.
- (EXHALES) Fine.
Just tell me which one
you think is best?
I hesitate giving you
any helmet,
as big a simp
as you turned out to be.
But what the fuck?
If you can do some good with it,
maybe take out a couple
of commies, some Blacks,
or papists, or a kike,
or something.
Better than sittin'
in this fuckin' closet.
Dad, that's not my thing. Um...
I do what I do
to st-- stop criminals,
- not a specific--
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah, sure.
(SIGHS)
♪ (CALM MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
So I forgot to close
the balcony door,
and when I came home,
my living room
was full of pigeons.
- (LEOTA CHUCKLING)
- Are you kidding me?
No. There was like ten of 'em,
and they shit all over my couch.
No. This guy.
(CHUCKLING) Did this dipshit
really show up
in full cosplay mode?
This is the guy
Waller's giving us?
- I told you she's fucking us.
- She's not fucking us.
- Is that an eagle
in his back seat?
- (MUFFLED SCREECH)
- (CHUCKLES)
- She's fucking us.
(BELL CHIMING)
HOST: Hi, sir, welcome in.
Oh, I'm with them.
Can I just grab a menu, please?
- HOST: Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (SIGHS)
Hey. Scooch. (GRUNTS)
- Why are you in your costume?
- (SCOFFS)
Costume? This is a uniform.
And it's brand new,
so I gotta stretch it out,
make it more comfortable
before I go on a mission.
Maybe I'm stupid, but why
would you even wanna wear that
on a mission?
A bright red shirt
and white pants
aren't exactly conducive
to lurking in the shadows.
People see this uniform,
it strikes fear in their hearts.
What people? The other people
at the Village People tryouts?
(CHUCKLES)
Why is there
a bald eagle in your car?
That's Eagly.
You guys ordered without me?
-"Eagly" is your pet eagle?
- Yeah.
- Is your dog named Doggy?
- (JOHN CHUCKLING)
- All right.
- Do you have a daughter
named Daughtery? (CHUCKLES)
Jealous of a guy's pet
eagle much?
- (HARCOURT CHUCKLING)
- Hey, sweet-cheeks!
Can you take
my order real quick?
- Sorry--
- Hi. Sure thing.
What can I get you?
Uh, mixed green salad,
and we'll do the garlic zoodles.
- Zoodles. Good choice.
- Thank you.
(INHALES DEEPLY) "Good choice."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- Zoodles are zucchini noodles.
-"Sweet cheeks"?
Seriously, dude?
She had cherubic cheeks.
It's a compliment.
"Sweet cheeks" is your butt.
- No, it's not.
- It is.
It's like calling somebody,
I don't know, "sugar tits."
That's totally inappropriate.
(SCOFFS) Her tits are
way too big to be sugar tits.
Sugar tits are, like, smaller,
perkier tits. Like...
yours. Uh, technically, I think
you may have sugar tits, too...
- Oh, yeah?
- ...but somehow that also feels inappropriate.
CLEMSON MURN: All right,
Peacemaker. That's enough.
You don't have to be happy
with this detail,
but you do have to treat
your fellow soldiers
- with respect.
- Yeah? Heard plenty of stories
about how you treat
people with respect, Murn.
Plenty.
Why is that busboy
staring at you?
I think that's my friend
Gut Chase's younger brother.
(WHISPERING)
He has mental issues.
Thank you. Just the
old shell game. (EXHALES)
- Take this home. Study it.
- What is it?
It's the dossier
on the first target.
- U.S. Senator?
- Don't look at it here.
Take our word for it,
the man's a serious threat
to the safety
of American citizens.
Oh, my God, could you at least
take you helmet off?
You're gonna get
dressing all over it.
Dressing is easier to get off
this helmet than a human lip.
That's a fuckin' fact.
You want to have a
dressing-getting-off contest
right now, Dye-Beard?
Okay, I don't dye my beard.
I've always
had unusually colored hair.
- Smith, just...
- (EXHALES) Jesus...
Fine. Fuck.
Are you always gonna be
this difficult?
Yep.
♪ (HARD ROCK MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Fuck yeah!
Peacemaker's back, baby!
♪ Twerk it, and twerk it
Get my little tush out ♪
♪ It's my famous butt dance
My butt dance, my butt dance ♪
♪ It's my famous b... ♪
- ♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
- Oh. Hey, man, what's up?
- Sup, Adrian?
- ADRIAN CHASE: Hey,
the-- the reason
I'm excited, it is normal.
Uh, I just found out this girl
that I'm seeing,
she's pregnant, you know?
You got a girlfriend?
Yeah. Uh, her name is Sharon,
uh, Osbourne. Uh, not--
not the one that you may know.
She's, uh,
a different one. The-- yeah.
Why are you always trying
to get me to set you up
with my cousin then?
Well, I wouldn't--
I wouldn't say, like,
-"girlfriend," you know?
- But you're happy
- she's pregnant?
- Yeah.
Because we are going
to have an abortion.
- DISHWASHER:
Well, yeah, good luck.
- Thank you. Yeah.
Hey, you're invited if you--
I don't wanna come
to your abortion, man.
ADRIAN: That's cool.
- Fuck yeah!
- ♪ (ROCK MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Peacemaker, baby.
- (EAGLY SCREECHES)
- PEACEMAKER: Aw, you missed?
Hey, bud. Learning to drive now?
- You gonna drive
us home? Yeah?
- (EAGLY SCREECHES)
LEOTA: It's friendly?
Oh, yeah.
- (CHUCKLES) I love animals.
- Yeah. Eagly is amazing.
- Hey.
- (SCREECHES)
- Hey, bud.
(SCREAMS) Just-- Oh, shit!
Man, I thought
you said it was friendly.
Oh, I thought you meant
friendly to me.
Yeah, I know it's friendly
to you. I saw you pet it.
You know, he was so happy
to see me today,
he wrapped his wings around me
and hugged me.
- An eagle hugged you?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I call bullshit on that.
You don't wanna believe
in miracles, that's on you.
- You're the new girl, huh?
- Yeah.
But I know my shit, don't worry
about that. I've done a lot of,
- you know, notable things.
- That's super vague.
Yeah, 'cause if I told you any
more, I'd have to, you know...
(IMITATES GUNSHOT)
- Kill me?
- Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLING) Oh, you hubbed up?
LEOTA: What?
- Married, yeah.
- PEACEMAKER: Hmm. That's cool.
I'm into old-fashioned stuff
too, you know,
Hummel figurines
and capital punishment...
- (CHUCKLES)
- ...and Garbage Pail Kids
and stuff.
- You know?
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Hey, what'd you mean
when you said you heard stories
about Mr. Murn?
I know he's a mercenary.
I know he killed
a lot of people,
and not always
for the right side.
I know I don't trust his ass.
Well, good night, Smith.
- 'Night, Arbysmola.
- (CHUCKLING) It's Adebayo.
- (EAGLY SCREECHING)
- Adebayo.
(CHUCKLING) Although
I do appreciate
the confidence
with which you said
something so wrong. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, that's my thing.
That and having a big dick.
LEOTA: Yep, information
I had no need for.
- (KEYS JANGLING)
- No, I'm-- I'm serious.
- (CAR DOOR OPENING)
- It's too big, actually. It...
- causes people pain.
- Okay.
Kids in junior high,
they called me "Chimp-Arm."
- Good night, sweet-cheeks.
- (CHUCKLES)
-"Sweet-cheeks."
- (CAR DOOR SHUTTING)
♪ ("COME ON COME ON"
BY NASHVILLE PUSSY PLAYING) ♪
That wasn't inappropriate,
was it, Eagly?
(SCREECHES)
♪ Baby woke me up this morning ♪
♪ She said
Hey, man, we are through ♪
- (SCREECHING)
- ♪ She said, if you ain't gonna
Go to heaven with me ♪
♪ Then I ain't goin'
To hell with you ♪
♪ Well, that's all right
Now baby ♪
♪ Just one last thing
On my mind ♪
♪ I'm just trying
To find a place ♪
♪ In a world
Gone mean and blind ♪
♪ So I say, come on
Come on, come on, fuck yeah ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Fuck yeah, come on
Come on... ♪
(CAR HORN HONKING)
♪ I said, come on, come on
Come on, fuck yeah! ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
- (LAUGHTER)
- ♪ ("SUMMERTIME GIRLS"
BY Y&T PLAYING) ♪
♪ Oh, yeah! ♪
CUSTOMER 1: Oh, woo-hoo.
(CHUCKLING)
- CUSTOMER 2: She's a babe.
- ♪ Oh, yeah, I... ♪
Hey, Goldilocks,
can I ask you a question?
As long as it's a question
about how to cure
- rotting fish breath, sure.
- Fuck you, bitch!
♪ I'm in love, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ At least
Every minute or two ♪
- CUSTOMER 3: Easy, buddy.
- ♪ Until the next time ♪
- ♪ A girl walks by ♪
- (EXHALES DEEPLY)
♪ I think I love her too
Oh, I ♪
- Hey!
- ♪ I can't help myself ♪
- Crazy coincidence, right?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Uncanny.
- Right? (CHUCKLES)
- What can I get you?
- PEACEMAKER:
I'll just-- I'll have the same.
- So... Harcourt, right?
- HARCOURT: Yeah.
PEACEMAKER: Thank you.
- What's your first name?
- Why?
Just curious. I mean...
(CHUCKLES)
You know, you don't have
to call me Peacemaker,
you can call me Chris.
I'll call you Peacemaker.
You call me Harcourt.
How's that?
Okay.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- CUSTOMER 1: You fucking
kidding me? She said what?
- PEACEMAKER:
I'm just trying to say...
- Hey.
...it doesn't always have to be
about work--
- Hold on.
- Okay.
What the fuck did you say
to my friend,
- you ugly fuckin cu-- (GROANS)
- (GRUNTS)
(BONES CRACKING)
Jesus fuck, lady. (GROANS)
- What was that next word?
"You ugly fucking" what?
- Oh, God!
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
Any of the rest of you wanna
finish it for him?
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
♪ Summertime girls ♪
♪ You make my whole world
Go around ♪
- What were you saying?
- Get off me! (WHIMPERS)
- (APPLAUSE)
- WOMAN: Aw, poor baby!
That was so fuckin' hot.
I clocked you driving by
and then making a U-turn
to follow me in here.
Come on, the way you say
it makes it sound all stalkery.
No, the way that you did it
made it stalkery.
I just described it.
Look, I have no interest in you
other than your ability
to fight for us.
Just because you're
handsome doesn't mean you're
not a piece-of-shit murderer.
- You think I'm handsome?
- Oh, my God, please fuck off.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Okay, look, I-- I've been
in prison
the last four years, okay?
I haven't been with anyone--
I-- I haven't been
with any woman in a long time.
I'm not asking
for emotional connection here.
I'm just asking for fun.
Genital-to-genital contact,
no touching above here.
No. Fuck it, it's gotta be here.
I gotta touch your boobs.
Sorry. Just trying to,
I don't know,
relieve some of the stress
that's been building up
over the years. I mean...
Cool! And I'm just trying
to fuckin' have a beer,
but whether
it's those douchebags or you,
I guess that's just something
that I can't have
in my life because,
I don't know, I wear makeup?
♪ ("NIGHT OF PASSION"
BY THE POODLES PLAYING) ♪
You know what?
Go fuck yourself...
- Chris.
- ♪ I feel your desire ♪
♪ As the moonlight lingers ♪
- ♪ In the sky ♪
- (SCOFFS)
♪ I'm walking through fire ♪
♪ Can't you hear me when I cry ♪
♪ One night of passion
One night of hunger ♪
♪ And my attraction
Is getting stronger... ♪
(BOTH MOAN, SCREAM)
- (SCREAMING) Freedom!
- ♪ My heart is
Screaming out your name ♪
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
WALLER: How's the team?
Okay, I guess. Murn,
I hear, is not such a great guy.
WALLER: I don't care
about the quality of the knife,
as long as the blade is sharp.
- John seems okay.
- WALLER: He's pliable.
Harcourt is hard.
WALLER: Barbie's ambitious.
Watch out for her.
Shouldn't we just loop them in
on the whole plan?
No. You're my eyes and ears,
Leota, while you're there.
And the only one I trust
with the big picture.
Did my forger get you the diary?
LEOTA: This goofy shit? Yeah.
Hide it in his trailer
the first chance you get,
somewhere he won't find it.
How's Peacemaker?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
He's his own thing.
- Sexist.
- WALLER: Yeah.
- Probably racist.
- Oh, you know who his father is.
LEOTA: Oh, yeah.
But there's something else
about him that's...
WALLER: What?
♪ (MELANCHOLIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
- ...sad.
- Empathy?
In this business, Leota,
that will get you killed.
Yeah, well, it doesn't really
matter, does it?
I appreciate the work,
but after this job is done,
Keeya and I will be back
on our feet
and I'll find a job
I actually like.
Sure.
Ignore your God-given,
natural talent.
Yeah, I don't think so.
I'm not like these people.
All right.
I have an early morning.
- Night, baby girl.
- Good night, Mom.
Waller's still trying
to pull you in, huh?
- Always.
- (SCOFFS)
(WATER RUNNING)
PEACEMAKER: Hmm.
Cool.
(GRUNTS)
Oh!
Oh, this-- this is my jam.
You know, this was back
when men were real men,
'cause they weren't afraid
to be women.
None of this
auto-tune, robots-dry-humping
that passes for music bullshit,
right? (CHUCKLES)
No way. Quireboys? Went to see
these guys when I was a kid.
God. I'd go to all the shows
when they came
through Evergreen.
♪ (“I DON'T LOVE YOU ANYMORE"
BY QUIREBOYS PLAYING) ♪
- ♪ I went to see her
Just this morning ♪
- (SINGS ALONG)
♪ To see how
The child might be ♪
♪ She sat there
Smoking all my cigarettes ♪
♪ At a table ♪
♪ Set for three ♪
♪ I could have cried
I could have cried ♪
♪ When she said ♪
♪ I don't love you anymore ♪
Hey, I gotta thank you
for tonight.
I was having a crazy,
fucked-up day,
but when I was in your pussy
back there,
I felt, I don't know,
fuckin' hope! (CHUCKLES)
That sound stupid? I just--
Maybe it's the big man
in the sky's way of saying,
"Chris, there's something more
for you out there,
you and Eagly,
other than all this rancid shit
life's thrown at you so far."
- ♪ So I went to
see my friends ♪
- (SINGING ALONG)
♪ I tried to turn
To them for help ♪
♪ And all that ♪
- ♪ Any of them said ♪
- ♪ All any of them said ♪
♪ You gotta look out
For yourself ♪
Well, fuck them!
♪ I could've cried
I could've cried ♪
♪ When she said ♪
♪ I don't love you anymore
I was slain and shown the... ♪
- (PIERCING SCREAM)
- What the fuck? Hey!
- (KNIFE SLASHING)
- (GRUNTS) Hold on. Hey. Hey!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GRUNTS)
- ♪ All the pain
Is with yourself ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- ♪ All the blame
Is with yourself ♪
- (SCREAMS)
(BLADE CLANGS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (CLATTERING)
- (GRUNTS) What the fuck?
- (INHUMAN ROAR)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(CRASHING, SPLINTERING)
(GRUNTS)
- (GROWLS)
- (GROANS)
♪ You're all I ever wanted ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- (VERTEBRAE CLICKING)
♪ Every time I see your face
Reminds me baby of what we had ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- (ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(SMASHING, CLATTERING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
♪ Always seemed in emptiness ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- (ATOMIZER HISSES)
(GRUNTS)
♪ I say my prayers every night ♪
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
♪ But even God don't care less ♪
- (BLOWS LANDING)
- (PEACEMAKER SCREAMING)
♪ I could've cried
I could've cried ♪
(GROANS) Fuck!
♪ When she said
I don't love you anymore ♪
♪ I was slain
And shown the door ♪
♪ Ain't no room here anymore ♪
- ♪ Please don't... ♪
- (PEACEMAKER SCREAMING)
- (FABRIC TEARS)
- (GRUNTS, GROANS)
♪ (DISTANTLY) All the pain
Is with yourself... ♪
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
"Take it easy," Doc said. Fuck.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
♪ (MENACING ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(ROARS)
(PANTS)
- (CAR DOOR OPENING)
- (SCREECHES)
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
(ROARS)
Activate sonic boom!
- (SCREAMS)
- (ENERGY PULSES, BOOMS)
(ENERGY FIELD BUZZING)
- (BUZZING STOPS)
- (PANTS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SIZZLING)
- (WINGS FLAPPING)
- (EAGLY SCREECHING)
(THUDS)
(CHUCKLES)
(EAGLY SCREECHING)
Thanks, Eagly.
♪ ("LOVE BOMB BABY"
BY TIGERTAILZ PLAYING) ♪
♪ You're not a lady
You're a love bomb, baby ♪
♪ Love bomb, baby
Come on, blow me away ♪
♪ Can't get enough
Of your sweet, sweet lovin' ♪
- (CHUCKLES)
- (SCREECHES)
♪ Keep it coming
Oh, baby, fire away ♪
♪ Ah ha-ah, oh yeah ♪
(SIRENS WAILING)
♪ Well, I've been
Waiting so long ♪
♪ For a girl like you
A time bomb ready to blow ♪
♪ I know it can't be wrong ♪
♪ 'Cause, baby
When I get you home ♪
♪ You're not a lady
You're a love bomb, baby ♪
♪ Love bomb, baby
Come on, blow me away ♪
♪ Can't get enough
Of your sweet, sweet lovin' ♪
♪ Keep it coming
Oh, baby, fire away ♪
♪ Love bomb, baby
Love bomb, baby ♪
Fire away, whoa! ♪
♪ You're everything I need
You're dangerous ♪
♪ You're blue-eyed dynamite
Sister TNT ♪
♪ You're the kinda love
I need tonight ♪
♪ Three, two one ♪
♪ You're not a lady
You're a love bomb, baby ♪
♪ Love bomb, baby
Come on, blow me away ♪
♪ Can't get enough
Of your sweet, sweet lovin' ♪
♪ Keep it coming
Oh, baby fire away ♪
♪ Love bomb, baby
Ah, ha-ah, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Direct hit
Target destroyed ♪
♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
This one will give you scabies.
Give me scab--
Why would I want scabies?
Challenge yourself.
Every man should have scabies
once in his life.
Okay.